ifonly.com 2016-10-24

# IfOnly | Extraordinary Experiences for Good

**IfOnly Privacy Policy**

**Last Updated: September 28, 2015**

Your privacy is important to us. Accordingly, we’re providing this Privacy Policy to explain our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that we receive when you use our Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third-party websites, services or applications.  Any information that we collect is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time that information is collected.  We may, however, modify and revise this Privacy Policy from time to time.  If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we’ll notify you of those changes by posting them on the Services or by sending you an email or other notification, and we’ll indicate when those changes will become effective.  Also, please note that, unless we define a term in this Privacy Policy, all capitalized words used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service.

**How do we collect and use information?**

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Services, to administer your use of the Services (including your Account, if you are a Member), to provide you with more relevant Experiences recommendations and otherwise improve the Services, and to enable you to easily offer, browse and purchase Experiences. 

Account Information. If you create an Account, we’ll collect certain information that can be used to identify you, such as your name, email address, postal address and phone number (“ **PII** ”). If you create an Account using your login credentials from one of your SNS Accounts, we’ll be able to access and collect your name and email address and other PII that your privacy settings on the SNS Account permit us to access. When you make purchases on our Site, we may store your billing information, purchase history and your credit card information.

Information Collected Using Log Files, Cookies and other Web Technologies.  Like many website owners, we use automated data collection tools such as Cookies to collect certain information. “ **Cookies** ” are small text files that are placed on your hard drive by a Web server when you access our Services. We may use both session Cookies and persistent Cookies to identify that you’ve logged in to the Services and to tell us how and when you interact with our Services. We may also use Cookies to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on our Services and to customize and improve our Services. Unlike persistent Cookies, session Cookies are deleted when you log off from the Services and close your browser. Although most browsers automatically accept Cookies, you can change your browser options to stop automatically accepting Cookies or to prompt you before accepting Cookies. Please note, however, that if you don’t accept Cookies, you may not be able to access all portions or features of the Services. Some third-party services providers that we engage (including third-party advertisers) may also place their own Cookies on your hard drive. Note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of Cookies and does not include use of Cookies by such third parties. 

Information Related to Use of the Services. Our servers automatically record certain information about how a person uses our Services (we refer to this information as “ **Log Data** ”), including both Account holders and non-Account holders (either, a “ **User** ”). Log Data may include information such as a User’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, the web page that a User was visiting before accessing our Services, the pages or features of our Services to which a User browsed and the time spent on those pages or features, search terms, the links on our Services that a User clicked on and other statistics. We use this information to administer the Services and we analyze (and may engage third parties to analyze) this information to improve and enhance the Services by expanding their features and functionality and tailoring them to our Users’ needs and preferences.

**What Information Do We Share With Third Parties?**

We will not share any PII that we have collected from you except as described below:

Information Shared when Using the Services.  There are various ways Members can make their PII publicly available through the Services or ways in which they can supply such information to Traina Interactive and other Members. Proving your PII and any other data through the Services, in connection with Experiences or to Traina Interactive whether you are Member or otherwise, is voluntary and should correlate with the degree of interaction you want to have with other users and Traina Interactive. 

When you apply to become a Luminary you will submit certain PII to us to complete your application.  If you are approved and become a Luminary, the PII you provide in your Experience Listing will be publicly available for viewing via the Services.  In connection with fulfilling in-person Experiences, as a Luminary, the contact information you provide for use on the day of the Experience will be shared with the purchasing End User.  As an End User, the PII that is shared with the Luminary depends on the type of Experience and information about you that is necessary to process your request. For example, when you purchase a physical Product your name and billing address, and the name, shipping address and phone number for the recipient of the Product, will be shared with the Luminary; and when you request to schedule an Experience, your name and any other required information indicated in the Experience Listing like the names of any other participants, the location address and other details necessary to schedule the Experience will be shared with the Luminary to process your request.  Luminaries are obligated to use your PII solely to fulfill the Experience and administer your related requests.  Luminaries and End Users also have the opportunity to communicate with each other one-to-one via our Services in connection with the purchase, scheduling and participation in Experiences.

Information Shared with Our Services Providers.  We may engage third party service providers to work with us to administer, provide and improve the Services. These third-party services providers have access to your PII only for the purpose of performing services on our behalf.

Information Shared with Third Parties. We may share aggregated information and non-identifying information with third parties for industry research and analysis, demographic profiling and other similar purposes.

Information Disclosed in Connection with Business Transactions. Information that we collect from our users, including PII, is considered to be a business asset. As a result, if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy or if we are acquired as a result of a transaction such as a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your PII may be disclosed or transferred to the third-party acquirer in connection with the transaction.

Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others. We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate: (i) to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas); (ii) to protect our property, rights and safety and the property, rights and safety of a third party or the public in general; and (iii) to stop any activity that we consider illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

Information We Disclose With Your Consent or at Your Request. We will share your information when you give us your consent to do so. For example, if you expressly request that we do so, we will share your PII with third-party sites or platforms, such as social networking sites.

**The Security of Your Information**

We take reasonable measures to protect the information that we collect from or about you (including your PII) from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Please be aware, however, that no method of transmitting information over the Internet or storing information is completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of any information.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Services may contain links to other websites and services. Any information that you provide on or to a third-party website or service is provided directly to the owner of the website or service and is subject to that party's privacy policy. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to such websites or services and we’re not responsible for the content, privacy or security practices and policies of those websites or services. To protect your information we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies of other websites and services that you access.

**Modifying Your Information**

You can access and modify the PII associated with your Account by emailing terms@ifonly.com. If you want us to delete your PII and your Account, please contact us at concierge@ifonly.com with your request. We’ll take steps to delete your information as soon as is practicable, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law.

**International Transfer**

Your PII may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you’re located outside the United States and choose to provide your PII to us, we may transfer your PII to the United States and process it there. 

**Our Policy Toward Children**

Our Services are not directed to children under 13 and we do not knowingly collect PII from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected PII of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as possible.

**Questions?**

Please contact us at terms@ifonly.com if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy.
